Cool. Now that we know that we can use
logging to debug our app, we're going to return to
this networking code snippet here and drop it into
the sunshine app to query for actual weather data. Open
up your project in main activity.java. In this class,
scroll down to the placeholder fragment class within the placeholder
fragment class in the on create view method, scroll down
and go ahead and add the networking code snippet here.
To get her blank, is pasted below again if you need it. You may need to enable
these options in auto import or add the imports
manually. See the instructions below. When you run the
app, you'll see that is crashes. Use log
cat to figure out which error is the guilty
culprit that caused the crash. We're assuming that for
this quiz question. You're using a device that's running
honeycomb or later. Use the emulator if needed.